itouchmap.com 2017-06-06

# iTouchMap.com Privacy Policy

iTouchmap.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: iTouchmap.com.

This site contains links to other sites. **iTouchmap.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

* * *

## iTouchmap.com works with third parties that serves ads to this site.

**Third Party Cookies** \- In the course of serving advertisements to this site, a third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

## Google

  1. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  2. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  3. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

* * *

### Google Maps API

As part of the services offered by iTouchmap.com we may display a map via the [Google Maps API](http://code.google.com/apis/maps/index.html). [Click here](http://www.google.com/privacy.html) to view Google's Privacy Policy.

* * *

### Map Location Services

On some map display requests there is an option, selectable by you, to use your current location for map centering. Location services are provided by your browser and typically there is an option available to you to enable or disable location services within the browser settings. Along with that option, usually the first time you display a location enabled map the browser will again ask for your permission to use your current location. Your current location is not used by in any way other than to center the map.

* * *

## Web Server Activity

Like most Web servers on the Internet, the iTouchmap.com server collects and stores within Web access logs all of the information that your Web browser sends when it requests a Web page, including:

  1. the name, domain, and numerical internet address of the host computer (typically a computer belonging to your Internet Service Provider and not your personal computer) from which you access the Internet;
  2. the date and time you accessed our site;
  3. the Internet address of the Web page that you came from;
  4. the page you requested from our site and the number of characters sent to your computer; and
  5. the information your Web browser software sends as its so-called 'User Agent,' which typically identifies the browser software and may also indicate the operating system used in your personal computer and the type of computer.

It is impossible to determine the actual identity of an individual user from this information. The logs are periodically summarized and analyzed to study site usage over time and to perform other studies to help us improve the site's organization, performance, and usefulness.

* * *

Please note that the iTouchmap.com website is visited daily by spiders (automatic robots used by Internet search engines) which index the site. Most of these spiders do not index email addresses. However, some of them do.

iTouchmap.com does not provide email addresses to other individuals or businesses.

## Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, then please [Contact Us](mailto:al@infosports.com).
